verican.us 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy

At Verican, we take your privacy very seriously. We are NOT in the business of selling, renting or disclosing your personally identifiable information to others. We have created this statement to describe our commitment to your privacy. 

## What information do we gather and track?

We record IP addresses (the Internet address of a computer) to track sessions on our site. Tracking gives us an idea of which parts and pages of our site users are visiting, how often they visit them, and how long they spend there. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that even if your session is tracked, you still remain anonymous. We also track browser type and platform. We use this information to deliver customized information specific to a particular platform and to determine the "mix" of browser types accessing our site. This information helps us make our site operate correctly with your browser. However, if you: 

  * Purchase a product from Verican
  * Sign up for a mailing list or enter a contest
  * Fill out a survey, or sign onto a page that requires authorization
  * Or enter into any other transaction with us,

you may be asked to provide us your name, e-mail address, phone number, fax number, postal address, credit card number (for purchases), and possibly other personal information. Additional demographic information may be optionally requested in order to improve our service to our customers. We may use the information you provide to: 

  * Keep you informed of new releases of our products.
  * Provide helpful hints and tips on how to use our products.
  * Make special offers that we extend only to our registered customers.
  * Improve our site and the services we offer you.

In limited cases, we may share your registration information (name, address, etc.) with the manufacturer of a product you purchase from us of -- but only when we inform you in advance of your purchase of the particular product. 

## Cookies and how we use them

Cookies are unique text files that are sent to your browser from a Web server. As you browse our web site, cookies are placed on your computer's hard drive to track the method of your referral to our site and whether you downloaded demo software and/or purchased software. The usage of these cookies is generally not linked to any personally identifiable information; however, if you demo or purchase a product from our web site, we may keep a record of how you reached our site to help us understand your interests and thereby serve you better. 

## How do we use the information we gather and track?

The information collected may be used for processing orders, personalizing the shopping experience, contests, promotions, newsletters, announcements, special offers, etc. 

## With whom may we share your information?

We may collect, create and disclose to third parties aggregated, anonymous statistics regarding our sales, traffic analyses and other information regarding or collected through our web site. This information won't include inpidually identifiable data about you. We may also sometimes engage agents or contractors to perform services necessary to our operations (for example, delivery of products, distribution of e-mail, etc.). When we do, we may give them access to name, addresses or other information necessary for them to do their job for us, but not for any other purpose. 

In limited cases when you buy a product from us, we may share your registration information (name, address, etc.) with the manufacturer of that product so they can get in touch with you. We will inform you in advance of any particular purchase for which such sharing will occur so you can decide whether you still want to make the purchase or to look at the manufacturer's privacy policy before deciding. Finally, in the event our company or its assets were ever sold, our customer database naturally would be transferred to the new owner. Except as described above, and except as may be required by law, we will not disclose your personally identifiable information to others without your consent. 

Finally, in the event our company or its assets were ever sold, our customer database naturally would be transferred to the new owner. Except as described above, and except as may be required by law, we will not disclose your personally identifiable information to others without your consent. 

## Choose or Opt-Out

**Announce Lists:** You can subscribe or unsubscribe from any of our product announce lists. These announce lists will be used to send subscribers any announcements (product upgrades, special offers, etc.) relevant to the list to which they are subscribed. 

**Registered Verican Customers:** Registered customers who do not wish to receive product announcements or special offers can contact Verican to update their account accordingly. 

## Correction/Updating Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if you no longer desire our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove your personal data provided to us. This can be accomplished by contacting Verican via e-mail, fax, phone or mail communication. 

## Links to Other Web Sites

This Verican site contains links to other Web sites. Although we do not provide any personally identifiable information to these companies, we cannot guarantee your privacy once you leave the Verican site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or content of web sites with links on our site. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any web site. 

## Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. However, some firewalls and certain versions of browsers don't permit communication through secure servers. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

## Registration

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

## Orders

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you. 

## Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

## Feedback or Questions

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, or have any questions or feedback regarding our privacy statement, please contact us as follows: 

Verican, Inc.  
850 South Boulder Highway #221  
Henderson, NV 89015  
415-296-7300  

## Privacy Policy Updates

Check back for updates to this privacy policy since we may update it from time to time without notice.
